José Martín Govea López

Front-End Developer

in www.linkedin.com/in/magovz
▶ https://martingovea.netlify.app

PROFILE

I am an IT engineer focused on Front End development with 5+ years of experience working with technologies like HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, TailWind CSS, JavaScript, React, Angular. I really enjoy what I do and I am looking for a job opportunity where I can contribute with my knowledge and grow personally and professionally.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer	04/2020 - 12/2022
Vive Metria	Ciudad Victoria,
 Design and development of web pages. 	Tamaulipas, México

• Development and maintenance of web applications.

· Obtaining requirements.

Software Developer	06/2018 - 09/2019
НТА	Ciudad Victoria,
 Creation and development of designs (Front End). 	Tamaulipas, México

• Development and maintenance of web applications.

Software Developer	09/2017 - 06/2018
DMAC	Ciudad Victoria,
 Design and development of user interfaces for web applications. 	Tamaulipas, México

Design and development of user interfaces for web applications.

• Design and development of web pages.

Software Developer 11/2015 - 12/2015 Budget Planning Department of Tamaulipas (professional practices) Ciudad Victoria, • Design and development of user interfaces for web and desktop applications. Tamaulipas, México

SKILLS

- Knowledge of HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Gulp.js.
- Experience with frameworks and development libraries (Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, React, Angular, Laravel, Django).
- PHP, Python.
- SQL.

PORTFOLIO

https://martingovea.netlify.app

LANGUAGES

Spanish English Native Intermediate

EDUCATION

Information Technology Engineer Universidad Politécnica de Victoria

09/2014 - 12/2017 Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México